<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jugador Rating</string>
    <string name="alert_title">Exit ?</string>
    <string name="alert_message">Are you sure you want to turn off this app ?</string>
    <string name="quote">"' Football is a dream where I never want to wake up from. '"</string>
    <string-array name="players_array">
        <item>Eden Hazard</item>
        <item>Karim Benzema</item>
        <item>Zlatan Ibrahimovic</item>
        <item>Marco Reus</item>
        <item>Totti</item>
        <item>Sergio Ramos</item>
        <item>Marcelo</item>
        <item>Luka Modric</item>
        <item>Marco Asensio</item>
        <item>Keylor Navas</item>
        <item>Iker Casillas</item>
        <item>Gianluigi Buffon</item>
        <item>Rakitic</item>
        <item>Manuel Neuer</item>
        <item>Mohamed Salah</item>
        <item>Franck Ribery</item>
        <item>Kylian Mbappe</item>
        <item>Lionel Messi</item>
        <item>Cristiano Ronaldo</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="eden">Eden Michael Hazard (born 7 January 1991) is a Belgian professional footballer
        who plays as a winger or attacking midfielder for Spanish club Real Madrid and captains
        the Belgium national team.</string>
    <string name="karim">Karim Mostafa Benzema born 19 December 1987) is a French professional footballer
        who plays as a striker for Spanish club Real Madrid and the France national team.</string>
    <string name="zlatan">Zlatan Ibrahimović born 3 October 1981)
        is a Swedish professional footballer who plays as a striker.</string>
    <string name="reus">Marco Reus born 31 May 1989) is a German professional footballer
        who plays as a forward for the Germany national team and Borussia Dortmund,
        where he is currently serving as the teams captain.</string>
    <string name="totti">Francesco Totti (born 27 September 1976) is an Italian former professional footballer who
        played for Roma and the Italy national team primarily as an attacking midfielder or second striker,
        but could also play as a lone striker or winger.</string>
    <string name="ramos">Sergio Ramos García (born 30 March 1986) is a Spanish professional footballer
        who plays for and captains both Real Madrid and the Spanish national team as a centre back. He has also played as a right back.</string>
    <string name="marcelo">Marcelo Vieira da Silva Júnior (born 12 May 1988), known as Marcelo
        is a Brazilian professional footballer for Spanish club Real Madrid and the Brazil national team.</string>
    <string name="luka">Luka Modrić (born 9 September 1985) is a Croatian professional footballer
        who plays as a midfielder for Spanish club Real Madrid and is the captain of the Croatia national team. He plays mainly as a central midfielder.
    </string>
    <string name="asensio">Marco Asensio Willemsen (born 21 January 1996) is a Spanish
        professional footballer who plays as a winger and attacking midfielder for
        Real Madrid and the Spain national team.
    </string>
    <string name="navas">Keilor Antonio Navas Gamboa (born 15 December 1986), known as Keylor Navas,
        is a Costa Rican professional footballer who plays as a goalkeeper for French club Paris Saint-Germain and the Costa Rica national team.
    </string>
    <string name="iker">Iker Casillas Fernández (born 20 May 1981) is a Spanish professional footballer
        who plays as a goalkeeper for Portuguese club Porto. Popularly dubbed "San Iker" ("Saint Iker")
        for his ability to produce spectacular saves, Casillas is widely considered to be one of the greatest goalkeepers of all time.
    </string>
    <string name="buffon">Gianluigi Buffon (born 28 January 1978) is an Italian professional footballer
        who plays as a goalkeeper for Serie A club Juventus. He is widely regarded by players,
        pundits and managers as one of the greatest goalkeepers of all time.
    </string>
    <string name="rakitic">Ivan Rakitić (born 10 March 1988) is a Croatian professional footballer
        who plays as a central or attacking midfielder for Spanish club Barcelona and is also the vice-captain for the Croatia national team.
    </string>
    <string name="neuer">Manuel Peter Neuer (born 27 March 1986) is a German professional footballer
        who plays as a goalkeeper and captain for both Bayern Munich and the Germany national team.
    </string>
    <string name="salah">Mohamed Salah Hamed Mahrous Ghaly (born 15 June 1992) is an Egyptian professional footballer
        who plays as a forward for Premier League club Liverpool and the Egypt national team.
    </string>
    <string name="ribery">Franck Henry Pierre Ribéry (born 7 April 1983) is a French professional footballer
        who plays for Serie A club Fiorentina.
    </string>
    <string name="mbappe">Kylian Mbappé Lottin (born 20 December 1998) is a French professional footballer
        who plays as a forward for Ligue 1 club Paris Saint-Germain and the France national team.
    </string>
    <string name="messi">Lionel Andrés Messi (born 24 June 1987) is an Argentine professional footballer
        who plays as a forward and captains both Spanish club Barcelona and the Argentina national team.
        Often considered the best player in the world and widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time.
        Messi has won a record six Ballon d_Or awards and a record six European Golden Shoes.
        He has spent his entire professional career with Barcelona, where he has won a club-record 34 trophies,
        including ten La Liga titles, four UEFA Champions League titles and six Copas del Rey.
        A prolific goalscorer and a creative playmaker, Messi holds the records for most goals in La Liga (431),
        a La Liga and European league season (50), most hat-tricks in La Liga (35) and the UEFA Champions League (8),
        and most assists in La Liga (173) and the Copa América (13). He has scored over 700 senior career goals for club and country.
    </string>
    <string name="ron">Cristiano Ronaldo dos Santos Aveiro (born 5 February 1985) is a Portuguese professional footballer
        who plays as a forward for Serie A club Juventus and captains the Portugal national team. Often considered the best player in the world
        and widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time, Ronaldo has won five Ballon d_Or and four European Golden Shoes,
        both of which are records for a European player. He has won 29 trophies in his career, including six league titles,
        five UEFA Champions Leagues, one UEFA European Championship, and one UEFA Nations League. A prolific goalscorer,
        Ronaldo holds the record for most goals scored in the UEFA Champions League (128) and the joint record of most goals scored in the
        UEFA European Championship. He has scored over 700 senior career goals for club and country.
    </string>

</resources>
